AMY MOSEMAN

812-320-4538 amoseman18@gmail.co m 550 Park Ln Buena Vista, CO 81211

PROFILE

Adventurer by heart, leader and problem solver by nature. I've worn many hats in my life which have given me the life lessons and experiences to mold me into a very adaptable and hard-working individual. Spending most of my working life in the hospitality industry, I know what is to be punctual, energizing, polite, calm, a multitasker and flexible. My work in the outdoor industry has given me the title of teacher, leader, steward, athlete, competitor, and risk manager. The volunteering work I do has taught me how to be an influencer with integrity, an enthusiastic motivator, and an organized and dependable communicator. All of these traits have made my transition into a web developer much smoother. The daily collaboration is a crucial part of the experience. I know I am a beneficial employee to any company I work for and will give you my full commitment.

EXPERIENCE

Elevation Beer Company, Poncha Springs, CO — July 2018- Present

Taproom employee that never hesitates to overlap in other fields serving the company's needs.

Canyon River Instruction, Salida, CO — May 2018 — Present

ACA certified instructor in Whitewater Paddle Rafting, Whitewater Oar Rafting, Swift-water Rescue and Stand Up Paddle-boarding. Teach multitude courses, including, women's specific, skills specific, kids and custom.

Elevate Her, Buena Vista, CO — June 2019 — Present

Volunteer with young local county girls to empower them through outdoor education. Trips include rafting, climbing, biking, skiing, hiking, camping, etc.

Monarch Mountain, Chaffee County, CO — Nov 2014 — April 2018

Bartender at high-volume, fast-paced ski resort. Responsible for serving duties, and running a solo overflow bar.

EDUCATION

University of Denver — Certificate in Full Stack Web Developing, 2021

REFERENCES

Andy Astor (303)-809-0964 | andy@elevationbeerco.com

Elisha McArthur (719)-480-4124 | elisha@canyonriverinstruction.com

Kristen Van Norman (970)-401-4210 || kristen@elevateherco.org